

# **SUMMARY**

I am a UI/UX Designer proficient in multimedia design and web • design. I have experience in studying user behaviors which have allowed me to develop my skills with application development. I also have a strong background/interest in product design.

#### **SKILLS**

- Wireframing & **Prototyping**
- Frontend Development
- **Usability Testing**
- **Product Strategy**
- User Research & Testing
- Persona & User **Stories**
- Visual Design
- UI/UX Design

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Web Designer**

Freelance, 2015-Present

- Designed and developed various websites, writing HTML, PHP, and CSS
- Delivered high-quality graphics for both print and web

# **Lauren Jeanne Photography**

2007-2020

- Founded fashion photography business while in High School
- Assigned various test photoshoots for modeling agencies

### **Sole Society**

Customer Care Representative, 2017-2018

- Provided customer support via emails, phone, and chat
- Assisted on multiple projects throughout departments

#### **Thrive Market**

Member Services Representative, 2017

- Provided customer support via emails, phone, and chat
- Monitored all social media platforms

#### **Poolside Concierge**

Web Designer, 2009-2011

- Created and managed website content
- Worked with the owner to recommend web copy for a target audience
- Updated entire site three times to account for expanding territory needs









#### **EDUCATION**

# **BLOC**

User Experience Design Program

Online program teaching the core principles of UI/UX design as well as frontend development for both desktop and mobile

# **PROJECTS**

# **Pixalist**

Role: UI/UX, Visual

Design

**View Project** 

# **Haves Club**

Role: UI/UX, IOS & Android Design

# **Scooters Coffee** Role: Visual Design

# Solace

Role: UI/UX, Visual Design, **Branding & Identity** 

**View Project** 

# InTheCloud

Role: UI/UX, Visual Design,

**Branding & Identity** 

View Project

### **TOOLS**









